Encounters are mysterious! But the world is even more so!
لقاءات البشر مغلّفة بالغموض، والعالم تلفّه طبقات أكثر حتّى
I'm so glad I'm with you!
!أنا مسرورٌ حقّاً لكوني معك
Today is a sad sisterly bond!
حلقة اليوم عن رابطة أختيّة حزينة
Have you solved the sealed room mystery?
أحللتم لغز الغرفة المغلقة؟
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ دماغه لبالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
On our way to Okino Yoko's concert, the old guy lost his ticket.
في طريقنا لحفلة أوكينو يوكو، فقد العمّ تذكرته
But he just happened to meet Aoshima Masayo,
ثمّ صادف فتاةً تُدعى آوشيما ماسايو
who promised to give him a ticket if he picked up her younger sister.
التي وعدت بإعطائه تذكرةً مقابل اصطحابه لشقيقتها الصغيرة
However, her sister, Aoshima Mina,
،لكنّ شقيقتها، آوشيما مينا
was found dead inside a completely-sealed bathroom!
وُجدت ميتةً في حمّام مغلق
Not only were the door and window taped from the inside,
فوق كون الباب والنافذة موصدين ،من الداخل بشريطٍ لاصق
but the word "goodbye" was spelled out in tape on the door!
كُتبت كلمة "وداعاً" بالشريط على زجاج الباب
Also, because only the sister's fingerprints were found on the tape,
ولاكتشاف بصمات الشقيقة وحدها ،على الشريط اللاصق
the old guy and Inspector Megure deemed it a suicide, but...
حكم العمّ والمفتّش ميغوري بأنّه انتحار
No! This wasn't a suicide!
!كلا، هذا ليس انتحاراً
Mina-san's killer was Masayo-san!
!المجرم الذي قتل مينا-سان هي ماسايو-سان
"The Sealed Bathroom Murder Case (Part 2)."
جريمة قتل الحمّام المغلق (الجزء الثاني)
Inspector Megure!
مفتّش ميغوري
So, did you check the convenience store angle?
إذاً، هل تأكّدت من متجر التموينات؟
Yes.
أجل
At around 7:00 last night,
،في قرابة الساعة السابعة البارحة
she bought two bathroom detergents, some tape, and two cans of beer.
اشترت مطهريّ حوض استحمام وشريطاً لاصقاً وعلبتيّ جعّة وفقما يبدو
Cans of beer?
علبتيّ جعّة؟
There were two empty cans in the kitchen, along with sleeping pills.
كانت هنالك علبتان فارغتان في المطبخ مع حبوب منوّمة
She probably couldn't work up the nerve to kill herself sober.
لعلّها لم تستطع استجماع الجرأة لقتل نفسها بوعيها
So, how did Mina-san seem when she bought it?
إذاً، كيف كان حال مينا-سان عند شرائها لها؟
Right... apparently, she seemed no different than usual. It's just...
،أجل، لم يبد عليها شيء بخلاف المعتاد ...ما بالأمر فقط
It's just what?
ما بالأمر... ماذا؟
Oh, no, it's nothing really.
ليس شيئاً مهمّاً
So it was clearly a suicide! Suicide, suicide!
!أي أنّه كان انتحاراً بالفعل! انتحار
Detective!
حضرة الضابط
It's just what?
ما بالأمر؟
Well, you see, the shop owner said something strange.
في الواقع، قال مالك المتجر شيئاً غريباً
As she was checking out, Mina-san...
...في نهاية حسابها، مينا-سان
By the way, Inspector. What time is it?
بالمناسبة حضرة المفتّش، ما الساعة الآن؟
Oh, the time?
الآن؟
See? Isn't that strange?
رأيت؟ أليس ذلك غريباً؟
But the room was sealed, and it seems clear it was a suicide...
لكن كانت الغرفة مقفلة، ويبدو أنّه جُزم بأنّه كان انتحاراً
You should tell the inspector! I bet it'll prove it wasn't... a suicide...
،أرى أنّ عليك إخبار المفتّش بذلك ...فلا بدّ أنّه سيثبت أنّه لم
Hey! What's that?!
انظر! ما ذاك؟
The peephole?
ثقب الباب؟
The black dirt above it!
!بل الوسخ الأسود فوقه
Th-This is a bloodstain!
!هـ-هذه بقعة دم
Bloodstain?!
بقعة دم؟
Y-Yes...
أ-أجل
But what's this doing here?
لكن لمَ توجد هنا؟
Mina!
!مينا
K-Kenji!
!كـ-كينجي
Is it... Is it true that Mina killed herself?!
...أ-أصحيحٌ
Yes...
أجل
But, Kenji! How did you know?!
لكن كيف عرفت يا كينجي؟
We informed him.
أخبرناه
He'd left a message on her machine at her estimated time of death.
فقد ترك رسالةً على آلة الردّ هنا في وقت الوفاة المقدّر
So I looked through her address book and called him here.
،فبحثت في دفتر عناوينها وطلبت قدومه إلى هنا
Why? Why would Mina commit suicide?!
!لمَ؟ لمَ قد تنتحر مينا؟
If I'd known this would happen,
،لو كنتُ أعرف حصول هذا
I would've broken through a window then!
!لحطّمت النافذة ودخلت آنذاك
"Then"?!
آنذاك؟
Did you come here last night?!
هل أتيت هنا البارحة؟
Yes! After I left my message!
أجل، بعدما تركتُ رسالتي
S-Seriously?!
!صـ-صدقاً؟
Yeah! I did!
أجل، صحيح
But no one answered the doorbell,
لكن لم يجب أحدٌ مهما قرعت الجرس
and I waited in front of the door awhile, but she never came home.
انتظرت فترةً أمام الباب، لكنّها لم ترجع
I figured she already went to bed and left!
فظننتُ أنّها قد نامت، ورحلت
And that's how I caught this cold!
ولذا أُصبت بهذا الزكام
Wait a minute! Does that mean...
...انتظر، أيمكن أنّ
...that bloodstain was...
بقعة الدم تلك؟
But isn't it strange to visit her after getting the answering machine?
لكن أليس من الغريب أن تأتي هنا بعلمك أنّها ليست موجودة؟
We had planned to have dinner together...
اتّفقنا على تناول العشاء معاً
And Mina always had the answering machine on.
وآلة ردّ مينا تعمل دوماً
Getting the machine didn't mean she wasn't home...
ردّها على مكالمتك لا يعني أنّ مينا ليست في البيت
But never mind that, Detective! Take me to Mina!
!ذلك جانباً، خذني بسرعة لمينا أيّها الضابط
A-Alright.
...حسناً
I see! So that's how it was!
!فهمت، هكذا إذاً
The trick to the room sealed with tape!
!حيلة الغرفة المغلقة بالشريط اللاصق
The intriguing bloodstain on the door!
!بقعة الدم الغامضة على الباب
And the strange feeling that was bugging me!
...والشعور الغريب الذي كان يراودني
I've figured it all out very clearly now!
فهمتُ كلّ شيء، أرى الصورة بوضوحٍ الآن
The killer was, without question...
...القاتل كان بلا شكّ
Without question, it was her, Masayo-san!
!بلا شكّ، هي! ماسايو-سان
She brought us here to complete this sealed room murder!
أحضرتنا إلى هنا لإكمال جريمة !قتل الغرفة المغلقة هذه
Unaware she's been holding definitive proof the whole time!
!في جهلها أنّها تحمل الدليل القاطع معها
Suicide, suicide! It was clearly a suicide, Inspector!
!انتحار، انتحار! كان انتحاراً بوضوح حضرة المفتّش
The tape on the inside of the door and window
باب ونافذة هذا الحمام كانا موصدين بشريط لاصق
completely sealed this room off.
من الداخل، مما جعله غرفةً مغلقة بالكامل
And judging from the dying words written in tape on that door
وبناءً على الشريط على زجاج الباب ...المُفترض بأنّه وصيّتها
and the fact only Mina-san's fingerprints are on the tape...
...ووجود بصماتها وحدها عليه
I can only think that she slit her wrist to commit suicide in here.
فلا يمكننا التفكير بغير أنّها قطعت معصمها هنا وانتحرت
Mori-san. Umm...
...موري-سان، أنا
Uhh, here...
هاك
The ticket to tonight's concert I promised you...
هذه التذكرة لحفلة الليلة التي وعدتك بها
Well, Inspector! I should be going!
إذاً حضرة المفتّش، سأنصرف الآن
Wait! Mori-kun! We haven't questioned you yet!
!انتظر، موري-كن! لم نستجوبك بعد
It's okay, it's okay! I promise to drop by the station after the concert!
!لا تقلق! سأمرّ بمركز الشرطة بعد انتهاء الحفلة
M-Mori-kun!
!موري-كن
Mister!
!يا عمّ
Don't tell me it's happening again?!
أيمكن أنّها أتت مجدداً؟
It? What?
أتت؟ ما هي؟
It just struck me. I've figured it all out.
لمع لي نورٌ للتوّ، وحللت كلّ شيء
I've figured out how the killer managed to seal this bathroom!
بما في ذلك حيلة القاتل !لإغلاق هذا الحمّام
Killer? You were just saying it was a suicide!
!القاتل؟ كنتَ تقول أنّه انتحار لتوّك
Yes, please forget everything I said earlier. I was only joking.
فلتنسوا كلّ ما قلتُه قبلاً من فضلكم، فقد كان مزحة
Sheesh.
...يا إلهي
Mina-san didn't commit suicide.
لم تقدم مينا-سان على الانتحار
She was murdered.
بل قُتلت
By you, Masayo-san! Her older sister!
!بأيدي أختها، أنت يا ماسايو-سان
Masayo-san?!
ماسايو-سان؟
H-Hey, now! Is it true, Masayo?!
!مـ-مهلك، أهذا صحيحٌ يا ماسايو؟
Don't be silly! You know I'd never kill my little sister!
!لا-لا تقل كلاماً سخيفاً كيف لي أن أقتل أختي؟
Besides, you should know more than anyone here
كما يُفترض أنّك تعرف أكثر من غيرك
that the bathroom was sealed off and we had to bust the door open!
بأنّ هذا الحمام كان مغلقاً عندما كان علينا فتح الباب عنوة
She's right, Mori-kun.
إنّها محقّة يا موري-كن
If you claim Masayo-san killed her, then would you mind telling us
إذا كنت تدّعي أنّ ماسايو-سان هي القاتلة، فلتخبرنا
how she miraculously managed to leave a completely sealed room?!
ما هي حيلتها الإعجازيّة التي استعملتها لمغادرة الغرفة المغلقة بالشريط اللاصق؟
Miraculously?
الإعجازيّة؟
It's nothing that special at all.
لم تكن شيئاً بذاك الإعجاز
The method is so extremely simple that anyone can do it.
إنّها طريقة بسيطة يمكن لأيّ أحد تنفيذها
First, Inspector. Please close the bathroom door for now.
إذاً حضرة المفتّش، فلتبدأ بإغلاق باب الحمّام من فضلك
Like that?
هكذا؟
How does the door look to you?
كيف يبدو الباب لك؟
H-How?
كـ-كيف؟
H-Hey! You don't mean--?!
أ-أيمكن، أتقصد؟
That's right.
أجل
The tape on the inside is placed on the glass in such a way
الشريط الملصق على الداخل موضوعٌ على الزجاج
to make it appear to be sealed from the inside.
بحيث يبدو أنّ الباب قد أُغلق من الداخل
Masayo-san used this illusion to her advantage.
استغلّت ماسايو-سان ذاك الوهم
Just because your answering machine is on
مجرّد عمل آلة الردّ
doesn't mean you aren't home.
لا تقتضي أنّك غير موجود بالمنزل
It's the same as that.
الأمر مثله
Then this door... was unsealed from the very start?
هذا الباب إذاً... لم يكن موصداً منذ البداية؟
Yes.
أجل
Masayo-san most likely knocked her sister out with sleeping pills,
أفقدت ماسايو-سان أختها وعيها بحبوب منوّمة غالباً
carried her in here, and taped up the window and door.
ثمّ حملتها لحوض الاستحمام، وألصقت الشريط اللاصق على الباب والنافذة
Then, after cutting her wrist...
...وبعد قطعها لمعصمها
...she forcefully opened the sealed door...
فتحت الباب المربوط بالشريط بالقوّة
...went out, and closed the door again.
وخرجت، وأغلقت الباب مُجدداً
The inside of the door is a blind spot!
الجانب الداخليّ للباب نقطة عمياء
If the tape had been undone beforehand,
ولو كان الشريط منزوعاً في الداخل منذ البداية
there'd be no way to tell when it happened once you went inside.
لا يمكنك معرفة متى حصل ذلك بعدما تدخل الغرفة
B-But you said you had a hard time getting inside!
!لـ-لكنّك قلت أنّك واجهت صعوبةً في الدخول
Yes, I was completely fooled by Masayo-san's acting.
أجل، خدعتني ماسايو-سان بتمثيلها تماماً
At that time...
...آنذاك
Ready, go!
...استعداد
...it was Masayo-san whose hand was on the knob.
كانت ماسايو-سان من تمسك بمقبض الباب
Turning the knob at just the right time,
أدارت مقبض الباب في التوقيت المناسب
she made it look like we had just forced the door open
وجعلتنا نستشعر أنّنا فتحنا الباب بالقوّة
and planted the idea in our minds that this room had been sealed off.
وزرعت إيهام كون هذا حيزاً مغلقاً في أذهاننا
Of course, she needed someone who'd fall for this trick for it to work.
كانت بحاجة لرفيق لجعل هذه الحيلة الذهنية تنطلي على الجميع بالطبع
That's why she brought us here. To act as a stand-in for Kenji-san.
لذا أحضرتنا هنا، مكان كينجي-كن الذي لم يستطع القدوم لإصابته بالزكام
B-But, Mori-kun!
لـ-لكن يا موري-كن
Only her sister's fingerprints were on these pieces of tape!
لم نجد إلّا بصمات شقيقتها المتوفاة !على الشريط اللاصق في الداخل
Plus, the end of each strip has prints
كما أنّ كلّ قطعة شريط احتوت
from both index fingers and thumbs!
!بصمات سبّابتها وإبهامها
How did that happen?!
!كيف تفسّر ذلك؟
Packing.
حزم الأمتعة
P-Packing?
حـ-حزم الأمتعة؟
Before killing her sister, Masayo-san had her help pack
قبل قتلها لشقيقتها، جعلتها ماسايو-سان تساعدها في الحزم
by tearing strips of tape off and lining them up.
وأخبرتها بقطع أجزاءٍ من الشريط اللاصق بطول ملائم وترتيبها
She then used that tape to seal the bathroom window and door
ثمّ استعملت تلك الأجزاء لإغلاق نافذة وباب الحمّام
and write out, "Goodbye."
"وتشكيل كلمة "وداعاً
Of course, she wore gloves to keep her own fingerprints off.
وهي ترتدي قفّازاً كيلا تترك بصمات بالطبع
As proof, there are cardboard boxes that had once been put together
ودليلاً لذلك، توجد صناديق كرتونيّة فتُحت قبلاً
and tape residue along the table that the strips had been affixed to.
وآثار أجزاء شريط لاصق مرتّبة على الطاولة
The examiner already knows about this, though.
رغم أنّ المحلّل يعرف ذلك سلفاً
Incidentally, Masayo-san. It was also you who sent your sister
بالمناسبة، كانت ماسايو-سان هي من أرسلت أختها
to buy the necessary tape and two bathroom detergents.
لشراء الشريط اللاصق ومطهريّ حوض الاستحمام الضروريين للجريمة
You first planned to seal the room
نويتِ إيصاد الغرفة أوّلاً
and kill your sister by mixing the two detergents together.
وقتل أختك بخلط المطهّرين
But she had bought the same types, which wouldn't produce a gas.
لكنّها اشترت صنفين متماثلين لا ينتجان غازاً
Having realized this after sealing the room,
،أدركتِ ذلك بعد إغلاقك للغرفة
you quickly chose to cut her wrist so she'd die of blood loss instead.
فقرّرتِ قطع معصمها سريعاً وجعلها تموت بفقدان الدم بدل ذلك
Or something along these lines, anyway, Masayo-san.
أو شيء من ذاك القبيل على الأرجح
M-Masayo?!
!ما-ماسايو؟
Yes... if it's just as you say, I could have done it,
،صحيح، إذا فعلتُ ما قلتَه فكان بمقدوري ارتكاب الجريمة
and I am most suspect, being a former resident as well as her sister.
وأنا الأكثر شبهة بصفتي ساكنة سابقة في المنزل، وشقيقتها
But did you see me seal the room with tape?
لكن هل رأيتني أغلق الحجرة بالشريط اللاصق؟
Did you see me cut my sister's wrist?
هل رأيتني أقطع معصمها؟
You can quibble all you want, but fantasy is still just fantasy.
يمكنك الهذي بافتراضاتك، لكن يبقى الخيال خيالاً
You have no proof at all.
لا يثبت شيئاً
After all, it's possible the room really was sealed shut with tape.
فمن المحتمل أنّ هذه الحجرة كانت مقفلةً بالشريط بالفعل
Isn't that right, Inspector?
ألستُ محقّة حضرة المفتّش؟
H-Hey! What now, Mori-kun?!
ما جوابك يا موري-كن؟
She's correct.
إنّها محقّة
D-Dad!
!أ-أبي
I have no clear proof whatsoever of this trick.
لا أملك دليلاً واضحاً على هذه الحيلة
Mori!
!موري
But...
...لكن
...there are signs that you killed your sister!
!تبقّت آثار على قتلك لشقيقتك
Definitive evidence that can't be explained away!
!دليلٌ قاطع لا يمكنك التهرّب منه
Wh-What, now?!
!ما-ماذا؟
Kenji-san. You said you came here last night.
كينجي-سان، قلتَ أنّك أتيت هنا البارحة، أليس كذلك؟
Y-Yes.
بـ-بلى
How long did you ring the doorbell, would you say?
كم أمضيت في قرع الجرس آنذاك؟
I rang it a lot.
طويلاً
She was late for our date, so I thought she might be sulking inside.
تأخّرت على موعدنا، فظننت أنّها مستاءة في الداخل
I see. It's just as I thought.
فهمت، كما ظننت
Wh-What is? What's "just as you thought"? Just come out with it!
ما-ماذا؟
Masayo-san. You were still at home at that time, weren't you?
ماسايو-سان، كنتِ لا تزالين في هذا المنزل آنذاك، أليس كذلك؟
And you checked on the annoying visitor through the peephole...
وتحقّقتِ من هويّة الزائر المزعج ...عبر ثقب الباب
...with your sister's blood still on you!
!ودم شقيقتك لا يزال عليك
Please check the front door.
فلتتفقدوا الباب الأماميّ
You'll find a bloodstain from then still there.
ستجدون بقعة دم وصلته من ذاك الوقت
Right, Detective Takagi?
أليس كذلك يا محقّق تاكاغي؟
Yes.
أجل
But... But so what?! My sister could've left that blood there!
!لكن... لكن ما في ذلك؟
Using something that vague as proof...
تستعمل شيئاً مبهماً لا تعرف متى ...وصل هناك ومن تركه كدليل
And you call yourself a great detect--?
...وتعتبر نفسك متحريّاً عظيماً
Yes... it's still there...
أجل، لا تزال موجودة
...a bloodstain that perfectly matches the one on the front door.
بقعة دم تطابق البقعة على الباب الأمامي بحذافيرها، ولشقيقتك
Masayo-san. It's right there on the black bandana around your head!
ماسايو-سان، إنّها على العصابة السوداء التي تربطينها حول رأسك
Now, would you mind explaining, Masayo-san,
حسناً، هلّا شرحتِ لنا يا ماسايو-سان
why your sister's blood is on that bandana
لمَ يوجد دم أختك على هذه العصابة
that came with a CD released yesterday?
التي صدرت مع قرصٍ مدمج بالأمس؟
B-But, Mori-kun!
،لـ-لكن يا موري-كن
How do you know she had the bandana on at the time of the crime?!
كيف عرفت أنّها كانت ترتدي !العصابة وقت الجريمة؟
The logo.
الشعار، صحيح؟
The logo on the bandana.
الشعار على العصابة
The real logo has a dash over the first "o" to lengthen the vowel.
للشعار الحقيقيّ شرطةٌ فوق حرف أو" الأوّل لمدّ الحرف"
The fact it's missing means something is covering it up.
اختفاؤها يعني أنّ هناك ما يغطّيها
My sister's blood must've landed there and covered it up.
لا بدّ أنّ دمّ أختي تطاير عليها، واسوّد فغطّاها
But how did you know, Mori-san?
لكن من المبهر أنّك عرفت ذلك يا موري-سان
You don't own a bandana of your own, right?
فلم تكن لديك عصابة بدورك، أليس كذلك؟
No... something always seemed off, but I couldn't put my finger on it.
،بلى، كان يراودني شعورٌ غريب لفترة لكن لم أستطع تحديد سببه بدقّة
Until I saw the logo on the key holder and the blood stain on the door
حتّى رأيتُ الشعار على حاملة المفاتيح وبقعة الدم فوق ثقب الباب
and learned that Kenji-san had rung the doorbell last night.
وعرفت أنّ كينجي-سان كان يقرع الباب البارحة
I see.
فهمت
So this key holder I showed off to you wound up being my downfall.
حاملة المفاتيح هذه التي أريتك إيّاها أدّت لهلاكي إذاً
Then you admit to the crime?
تعترفين بالجريمة إذاً؟
Yes, take me down to the station or wherever.
أجل، خذني لمركز الشرطة أو أينما شئت
B-But why would you kill Mina?! You were such close sisters!
!لـ-لكن، لمَ قتلتِ مينا؟ !كنتما شقيقتين مقرّبتين جدّاً
I guess we were too close.
ربما مقرّبتين أكثر من اللازم
My sister Mina was always following in my footsteps.
لطالما كانت شقيقتي مينا تتبع آثاري
She'd like the same idols I did, buy the same bags and clothes I did,
أحبّت نفس الفنّانين مثلي، واشترت نفس حقائبي وثيابي
she'd even copy the furniture and dishes I had!
قامت بتقليد أثاثي وأوانيي حتّى
At first, I thought it was cute. She was my little sister.
،رأيتُ أنّ ذلك كان ظريفاً في البداية فهي شقيقتي الصغيرة
But, one day, after it started to get on my nerves,
لكن في إحدى الأيام، بعدما بدأ الأمر يغيظني
she smiled with an innocent look on her face and told me...
،ارتسمت على وجهها ملامح بريئة ...وأخبرتني بهذا وهي تبتسم
I'm sorry, Sis!
!آسفة يا أختي
I fell in love with the same person you like and confessed to him!
وقعتُ في حبّ نفس الشخص !مثلك مُجدداً، واعترفت له أخيراً
Wait! Does that mean--?!
...لحظة، أتقصدين
Yes, that's right. It was you, after we had gone out for five years!
أجل، كان أنت يا كينجي بعد تواعدنا لخمس سنوات
So we wound up competing for you,
كانت تتنافس معي بالأصل لا أكثر
and in the end, she and you got engaged
وفي النهاية، خطبتما بعضكما
and I had no choice but to move out.
وكان عليّ مغادرة هذا المنزل
I wanted to get rid of the little devil who stole everything from me!
أردتُ التخلّص من تلك الشيطانة !الصغيرة التي سلبت كلّ شيءٍ منّي
I wanted her out of my sight!
!أردتُ إزالتها من ناظري فوراً
Y-You have it wrong, Masayo!
!أ-أخطأتِ يا ماسايو
I was the one who insisted on getting married!
!كنتُ من تقرّب لها، وضغط عليها الزواج
She kept turning me down, of course!
رفضتني باستمرار بالطبع
She said she wanted to focus on patching things up with her sister.
وطلبت منّي إصلاح علاقتي معك بدلاً منها
Y-You're lying! She said she kept insisting on getting married!
هـ-هذه كذبة! فقد قالت أنّها !من تقرّبت منك
That was the condition she gave when she accepted my proposal.
كان ذلك شرطها عندما قبلت بخطبتي لها
She didn't want you to know I chose her over you,
لا بدّ أنّها لم ترد أن تعرفي أنّي فضّلتها عليك
because you have more pride than most people!
ففخرك أعلى من غيرك
Stop with this nonsense! She was too selfish to ever think about me...
توقّف عن هذا الهراء! من المستحيل ...أن تراعيني فتاة أنانيّة مثلها
There's no way to know your sister's true feelings now,
لا سبيل لمعرفة مشاعر شقيقتك الحقيقيّة الآن
but it's clear she really cared about you.
لكن لا شكّ أنّك كنتِ عزيزةً عليها
Wh-What would... What would you know?!
...ما-ما
The convenience store owner said this...
...قال مالك متجر التموينات
While he rang up her items,
أنّه في نهاية حساب شقيقتك
your sister went to get a different detergent.
ذهبت لاستبدال أحد المطهرين
To get a kind that wouldn't accidentally produce chlorine gas
بآخر بحيث لا ينتج غاز كلوريّ عن غير قصد
if you mixed it with the other one.
إذا خلطتِهما معاً
To protect your life.
لحماية حياتك
Th-That can't be...
...لا-لا يمكن
Th-That can't be true...
...لـ-ليس صحيحاً
Mina!
!مينا
Hey! Hey! Mina!
...اسمعي
Tell me it's not true!
!أخبريني أنّ ذلك ليس صحيحاً
Mina! Mina!
!مينا! مينا
Mina!
!مينا
Kindness brought forth hate and transformed into murderous intent...
أثار لطفٌ مشاعر كره، وتحوّل لإرادة إجراميّة
Amid the echoes of the sinner's regretful cries,
،بين أصداء صرخات بكاء الآثمة المتعصّرة ألماً
twin cups and toothbrushes sat quietly by each other at the mirror.
تجاور كأسان وفرشتيّ أسنان بصمت أمام المرآة
As if they had forgotten the happy memories
كما لو أنّهما نسيا الذكريات السعيدة
of when they had once been used.
لزمن استعمالهما قبلاً
Encore! Encore! Encore!
!عرض آخر! عرض آخر! عرض آخر
Yoko-chan!
!يوكو-تشان
Mori-san!
!موري-سان
You really came!
!أتيتَ بالفعل إذاً
But of course!
!بالطبع
I'm so happy!
يسعدني ذلك
Don't, Yoko-chan!
!كلا
You shouldn't act that happy in front of your fans!
لا يجدر بك أن تقومي بشيء !مُسعد كهذا أمام معجبيك
I dunno why, but he's smiling while he's sleeping.
لا أدري لمَ، لكنّه يبتسم في نومه
He must be having a dream where he made it to the concert.
لا بدّ أنّه يحلم بحلم حضر فيه الحفلة
Really, you shouldn't!
!لا يصحّ
Yoko-chan!
!يوكو-تشان
Newscaster Aki-san is missing?! Was she threatened?!
المذيعة آكي-سان مفقودة؟ أتلقّت تهديداً؟
No, she didn't seem afraid at all then!
كلا، لم يبد أنّها خائفة أبداً آنذاك
If that call had been a trap to lure her somewhere--!
ماذا لو كان ذاك الاتّصال !فخّاً لاستدراجها إلى مكان؟
End of the line!
!هذه هي النهاية
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
Next Conan's hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Pager.
جهاز مناداة
Next episode is about a pretty weather girl.
!الحلقة القادمة عن مذيعة طقس جميلة
Watch me go wild.
!سأريها قصارى جهدي
Whoa there.
مهلك